[
    {
        "question": "Who will be the 'fun' parent?",
        "choices": ["Onika", "Abul", "Both", "Neither"],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What food will the baby most likely to crave based on the parents?",
        "choices": ["Fanta", "Nugets", "Pizza", "Coke", "Waffle"],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Who will be more likely to sneak baby snack?",
        "choices": ["Abul", "Onika"],
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Who will the baby more likely to look like?",
        "choices": ["Mum", "Dad", "No Idea"],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Who will be the more protective parent?",
        "choices": ["Onika", "Abul", "Both", "Neither"],
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Who will be the more organised parent?",
        "choices": ["Onika", "Abul", "Both", "Neither"],
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Who will change more diapers?",
        "choices": ["Onika", "Abul", "Both", "Neither"],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Who will fall asleep during story time?",
        "choices": ["Onika", "Abul", "Both", "The baby"],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Who will be more likely to spoil the baby?",
        "choices": ["Onika", "Abul", "Both", "Neither"],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What will be the baby's favorite bedtime snack?",
        "choices": ["Milk", "Cookies", "Fruits", "Chips"],
        "answer": 0
    }

]
